They’ve got a story, but have lost the plot.
Lost in La Mancha is a documentary film directed by Keith Fulton.
Fulton and Pepe's 2000 documentary captures Terry Gilliam's attempt
to get The Man Who Killed Don Quixote off the ground.
Back injuries, freakish storms, and more zoom in to sabotage the project.
Narrator (voice), played by Jeff Bridges.
Self, played by Johnny Depp.
Self, played by Vanessa Paradis.
Self, played by Jean Rochefort.
Self - Writer & Director, played by Terry Gilliam.
Self - Co-Writer, played by Tony Grisoni.
Lost in La Mancha is a 2002 documentary film about Terry Gilliam's first attempt to make The Man Who Killed
Don Quixote, a film adaptation of the 1605/1615 novel Don Quixote by Miguel de Cervantes.
The documentary was shot in 2000 during pre-production and filming and it
was intended as a "making-of" documentary for the film.
However, Gilliam's failure to complete his film resulted in the documentary filmmakers
retitling their work as Lost in la Mancha and releasing it independently.
Written and directed by Keith Fulton and Louis Pepe, Lost in La Mancha presents Gilliam's
effort to make Don Quixote as a parallel to Quixote's quest to become a hero.
It co-stars Johnny Depp, Jean Rochefort, and Vanessa Paradis, who
were cast as stars for The Man Who Killed Don Quixote.
It is narrated by Jeff Bridges.
Gilliam ultimately succeeded in making The Man Who Killed
Don Quixote, which was released in 2018.
Fulton and Pepe have made a follow-up documentary, titled He Dreams of Giants,
which covers Gilliam's entire scope of work on the Quixote project.
The film explores themes of director, don quixote, cinema history.